We're sick and tired of you dodgin' the issue!
（数藤）だから！　そんな
ごまかしなんか　いらねえんだよ！！
（亞里沙）ごまかしてなどいません。事態が　はっきりするまで→
I am not dodging the issue!
I'm saying that we shouldn't take any
rash actions until our situation becomes clear.
性急に動くべきではないと
言ってるんです。
We should be hearing before long
（亞里沙）間もなく
私の祖父　供奉院家からも→
from my grandfather, head of the Kuhouins.
連絡が来るはず。
もう少しの辛抱です。
We only need a little more patience!
Come on, let's face facts here!
（数藤）
もっとよ　事実を見詰めようぜ。
どうせ　もう　俺たちは
存在しないことになってんだよ！→
We officially don't exist anymore!
ウイルスと一緒によ
始末されんだ！
They're gonna kill us along with the virus, get it?
We're all gonna die!
みんな死ぬんだ！
おしまいなんだよーっ！！
It's all over for us!
うぅ…。　うっ！
Hey, cut it out! Nobody knows that for sure!
ちょっと　やめてよ！
そんなの誰も分かんないじゃない！
That's right, don't shout.
そうです。　怒鳴らないで。
I asked everyone not to take
the floor until they had the mike.
発言は　マイクを受け取ってからとお願いしたはずです。
（難波）僕が思うに→
The way I see it,
our biggest problem right now
is that we don't know the situation.
状況が分からないことが
今　最も問題だと思うんです。
Shouldn't someone take responsibility
誰かが責任を持って　環七のウォールを視察してくるべきでは？
and go inspect the Loop 7 wall firsthand?
Yeah! He's right!
（生徒）そうだ　そうだ！
（生徒）難波君の言うとおり！
- Nanba's right!
- You go!
Why does little miss president
take guys like that seriously?
（鶫）何で　あんな連中　まともに
取り合っちゃうかな　会長ちゃんは。
I don't know if that's integrity or stupidity...
（鶫）律義っつーか　何つーか。
She's just trying to hear everybody out!
What's wrong with that?
（颯太）ちゃんと　みんなの話を
聞こうとしてるだけだろ。
いいじゃんか！
（鶫）平和なときならね。
Nothing, in peacetime.
（いのり）集。　どうしたの？
What's wrong, Shu?
（集）あっ。　いや…。
Nothing...
I was just wondering what
Gai would do at a time like this.
もし　涯がいたら
こんなとき　どうするかな？　って。
Please!
（生徒）「お願いです！
何とかしてください」→
Please do something!
I want to see my mama and papa!
「パパとママに会いたいんです！」
フン！
What we're saying
何であれ　会長には　行動の方針を
決めてくれってことです。
is that we want you to decide
on some kind of course of action.
If you ask me, " Grandpa will
come and save us, so just wait for him"
「おじいさんが　助けに
来てくれるから　待って」なんて→
isn't a very leader-like thing to say. Am I right?
リーダーの発言とは思えない。
そうでしょ？
- Good point.
- What are you, a kid?
≪（生徒）確かに。
≪（生徒）子供かっつーの！
Pursuant to Article 32,
Section 3 of the student council charter,
（難波）生徒会規則
第３２条　第３項に基づき→
生徒会長の不信任決議　ならびに
新会長の選出を要求します。
I'm hereby filing a no-confidence
resolution against the president
and requesting that we elect a new president.
♪♪～
Houkai no shinfonii ga narihibiite
Furu ame wa maru de namida no neiro
Kizuite
Sono me wa tagai wo mitomeru tame
Sono koe wa omoi wo tsutaeru tame
Sono te wa daiji na hito to tsunagu tame ni aru
Kono uta ga kikoeteru
inochi aru subete no mono yo
Shinjitsu wa anata no mune no naka ni aru
Arashi no umi wo yuku toki mo
Keshite okusuru koto no nai tsuyosa wo
Kureru kara
It's time to distribute the vaccine.
[ﾏｲｸ]（祭）ワクチン配布の時間です。
Turbulence
（祭）今週の割り当ての人は
お昼休み時間中に→
Everyone allotted a dose this week,
report to the student council room on
the fourth floor before lunch hour ends.
忘れずに　４階の生徒会室まで
来てください。
Here you go. Take good care of it.
（綾瀬）はい。　大事に使ってね。
（谷尋）ついに噴き出したって
感じだな。
I think the dam's finally burst.
Dam? What dam?
（颯太）噴き出るって　何がだよ？
（谷尋）裏サイトの
天王洲アンダーグラウンド。　見てみろ。
This is the school's unofficial website,
Tennozu Underground. Take a look.
（颯太）えっ　ネット復活してんの！？ホントだ。
The internet is back?!
Wow, it is.
The jamming suddenly lifted on just
the school's local network, and it's back up.
（谷尋）学内のローカルネットだけ　ジャミングがいきなり解除されて　復活した。→
外とは相変わらずだ。
（花音）見せて　見せて。
We're still cut off from the outside.
Let me see, let me see!
（颯太・集・花音）あ…。
"What do you make of Kuhouin???"
"She's not cut out to be a leader!"
They're really targeting the president.
（花音）会長　結構
やり玉に挙がってるね。
"More like, is she stupid?"
"Maybe she's not as good as she looks..."
But she's working hard! That's just mean!
（颯太）ちゃんと頑張ってんのに
ひでえよな！
"This just means she doesn't have what it takes in
a crisis... what we want most is a fast decision!"
I can see their point, though.
（鶫）分かんないでもないけど。→
I mean, she's not really cut out for leadership.
会長ちゃん　あんまり
リーダー向きじゃないし。
Hey!
おい！　そんな言い方　ないだろ？
俺たちの大事な仲間じゃんか！
That's a horrible thing to say!
She's one of us, and we care about her!
"One of us"? It's only circumstances
that forced us together.
「仲間」って…。　別に　行き掛かり上一緒にいるだけだし。
You are so not cute!
（颯太）かわいくねえ！
Bleh!
ベェーだ！　悪うござんした！
I'm so sorry!
Tsugumi!
（花音）鶫ちゃん！
（颯太）何だよ　あいつ！
What's her problem?
Gather as much info on the outside and
as many people who want to leave as you can.
（難波）外の情報と　出たいって
意見を　できるだけ集めろ。
We'll confront her with that at the assembly.
総会で突き付けてやる。
（数藤）そんなんより→
Whatever, why not just do
the uppity bitch already?
いっそ　やっちゃわない？
あの高慢女。
Don't get hasty. We can play
our trump card whenever we want.
慌てるなよ。
奥の手は　いつでも使えるからな。
（鶫）ねえ　いのりん。
Hey, Inoreen.
いのりんはさ
家族って　いないよね。
You don't have any family, right?
Have you ever felt lonely?
（鶫）さみしいと
思ったことってある？
Only once.
一度だけ…。
One time Shu wasn't there and I was cold.
集がいなくて
寒かったことがあったの。
Gai told me that's "loneliness."
それが「寂しい」だって　涯が。
Thanks for sharing.
ごちそうさま。
Are you lonely?
寂しいの？
鶫は　寂しい？
Tsugumi, are you lonely?
N-No, of course not!
I mean, sure, Funeral Parlor is gone...
そ…　そんなこと
あるわけないでしょ！
そりゃ
葬儀社は　もう　ないけど…。
But I lived on my own
the whole time before that.
私は　その前から　ずっと１人で
生きてきたんだもん。
いまさら
さみしいとか　ないわよ！
I'm way past being "lonely" or whatever.
Yeah...
（鶫）《そうよ》→
《私は　ずっと
１人だったんだから》
I've always been alone, so...
（鶫）だから　余計な心配とか
しなくていいからね　集！
So you don't have to go
around worrying about it, Shu!
R-Right!
はい！　あっ。
フフ。
ちょうどいいわ。　これ　あげる。
Perfect timing. I'll give you this.
ゲノムレゾナンスゲージ？
そう。
"Genomic Resonance Gauge"?
Yep. To put it bluntly, it's like
a gadget for measuring Void strength.
ぶっちゃけ言えば　ヴォイドの
強さを測る装置みたいなものね。
昨日　攻めてきた連中の
車のそばに落ちてたの。
It was lying on the ground near
the truck those guys attacked us in yesterday.
Hmm.
ほう。
（鶫）トータルの数字が大きいほど→
Seems like the bigger the total number,
the more butt the Void kicks.
すごいヴォイドが出せる
ってことみたい。
I see...
（綾瀬）なるほどー。
すごい　すごい！
Impressive!
Wh-What?! What is it?!
な…　何？　何なの！？
（綾瀬）そういえば
鶫のヴォイドって…。
Come to think of it, what is Tsugumi's Void?
Well, I've never drawn it out...
出したことはないけど…。
えっ…。→
ええっ！？
（綾瀬）こんな状況だもの。
Think of the fix we're in.
みんなのヴォイドを
把握しておいた方がいいわよね。
It's best to get a good idea
of everyone's Voids, isn't it?
（祭）大丈夫。
痛いのは最初だけだから。
Don't worry; it only hurts for a second.
痛いの！？
It hurts?!
All right, Dr. Ouma, have at it!
（花音）それじゃ　桜満先生　どうぞ！（鶫）ちょ…　待っ…。
Hey... wait...
Okay, then... Sorry, Tsugumi.
それじゃ…。　ごめん　鶫。
St-Stop... No!
嫌…。　やめ…。→
嫌ああああああ！！
（茎道）報告を。
（ローワン）「はっ」→
Report.
Yes, Sir. We're deploying a mop-up
team based on your strategy outline.
「閣下の作戦概要に基づき
掃討部隊を配置」→
Next we'll form a ring around them
to purify and shrink the blockade zone.
「その後　円環状に封鎖区域を
浄化　縮小していきます」
（嘘界）主力には　先日　頂いた
データを基に創設した→
For our main force, I've strategically stationed
the Ghost unit I formed based on
the data you gave me the other day.
Ｇｈｏｓｔ部隊を配しました。
（嘘界）では　閣下。
Now then, Mr. President...
Begin.
（茎道）始めたまえ。
（ローワン）「はっ！」→
Yes, Sir!
Now beginning Operation Purify Tokyo!
「東京浄化作戦　開始します！」
≪（警報）
おっ？
This is an announcement from
the new Japanese government.
[ﾏｲｸ]（アナウンス）こちらは
新日本政府です。→
As of midnight tonight, we are shrinking
the area of the quarantined zone.
本日　午前０時をもち
隔離区画を縮小いたします。→
Anyone who attempts to
venture outside the red lines
赤いラインより外へ
出ようとした場合→
will be purified on sight, so please be careful.
無警告で浄化処理されますので
ご注意ください。
（どよめき）
（銃声・悲鳴）
I don't like this.
≪（ダリル）気に食わないなぁ。
（ダリル）大統領命令か何か
知らないけど→
President's orders or not,
there's no love in this killing style.
殺し方に愛がないよ。
And that "Ghost unit"...they're not
connecting from here, are they?
あのＧｈｏｓｔ部隊ってのも
ここから接続してないよね？→
And they're not on the scene, either...
臨場してるわけでもないし…
オペレーターは　どこにいるわけ？
So where are the operators?
（ローワン）機密事項だ。
That's top-secret.
♪♪～
（難波）本当なのか？
（生徒）高円寺らしいです。
Is it true?!
At Koenji, they say.
（難波）虐殺…。
"So the government's started
a slaughter over by Koenji?"
Slaughter...
"I heard the people trying
to get help all got killed."
（数藤）こりゃ
いよいよ　マジでヤバいぞ。
Things are gettin' seriously bad now.
"I heard they lynched anybody
and everybody there! Scary..."
"It's all over now... Everybody's dead."
Nanba.
≪（生徒）難波さん。
What are you up to at this time of night?
（亞里沙）何をしてるんです？
こんな夜中に。
高円寺で虐殺って噂ですよ。
Rumor has it there's been a slaughter at Koenji.
（難波）どうするんです？　それでもまだ　動かずに待ちますか？
What now? Do you still
want to wait and do nothing?
（嘘界）ローワン君。→
Rowan.
かつて　ギリシャの都市国家群を
滅ぼしたものが→
Do you know what brought
down Greece's ancient city-states?
何だか知っていますか？
２文字で。
In a word.
あいにく　物理学専攻で…。
I'm afraid I majored in physics.
Demagogy.
（嘘界）「デマ」ですよ。
Look what starts happening
the moment we stop jamming their signals.
ジャミングを解いてあげたら
真っ先に始まったのが　これです。→
そして…。
さあ　どう反応しますかねぇ。
And...
Now, I wonder how they'll react?
悪趣味ですね。
（嘘界）あまり褒めないでください。
You're a perverse man, Sir.
Please, don't compliment me too much.
Thanks a ton, Gramps.
（アルゴ）助かったよ　じいさん。
（アルゴ）いいかげん
逃げ回るのも限界だったし。
We couldn't have made it on the run much longer.
（大雲）このご恩には
どう報いれば？
How can we repay your kindness?
（供奉院）茎道の就任と同時に→
All lines of communication
and transport into the city center
were shut down as soon as Keido took office,
都内との連絡や　輸送手段が
完全に断たれたが→
まだ　たくさんの人間が
生き残っておるはず。　助けたい。
but there should still be plenty of survivors left.
I want to save them.
It will be our pleasure to assist you.
（大雲）
喜んで協力させてもらいます。
（生徒）おい　見ろ！
Hey, look!
（生徒）「これは確実なソース！」
「外に出たヤツから」
"This is from a solid source...
someone who got outside"!
（生徒）「葬儀社のメンバーを
差し出せば→
"If you hand over Funeral Parlor members...
...you can get outside the wall"?!
ウォールの外に出られる！！」
（祭）集。　聞いた？　高円寺の…。
"Student Body Meeting Today!!!"
Shu, did you hear about Koenji?
"There will be a vote of no-confidence in
student council president Arisa Kuhouin
and an election of our next president."
Yeah. It still might just be a rumor, but...
うん…。
まだ噂かもしれないけど。
《でも　やりそうだ。
アンチボディズなら》
But it's the kind of thing
the Anti Bodies would do.
（祭）どうなっちゃうんだろう？
この学校も…。
I wonder what's going to happen to our school...
It's okay.
大丈夫だよ。
これ以上
悪いようにはならないよ。
It won't get any worse than this.
We've got everyone with us,
and I'll fight too if I have to.
みんなも　いるし。
僕も　いざとなったら戦うしさ。
じゃあ　もし　集がケガしたら→
Okay then, if you get hurt,
I promise to heal you with my Void!
私が　ヴォイドで
必ず治してあげるね。
ありがとう。
でもさ　集は→
Thanks.
But Shu, don't you want to be the leader?
自分がリーダーになろうとは
思わないの？
えっ…。
（祭）立候補したら？　生徒会長。
Why not run for student council president?
そんな　無理だよ。
Nah, it would never work.
人に命令して
何かやらせるのなんて→
I'm the last guy cut out for giving people
orders and making them do stuff.
僕　一番　向いてないんだから。
That's not true! You've just
convinced yourself it's true.
（祭）そんなことないよ！
自分で　そう思い込んでるだけ。
あ…。
集は　なれるよ。　王様に。
You can be a king, Shu.
（鶫）ホ～ッホッホ！→
Now you're what I'd call a real "soothing girl"!
これぞ　ホントの癒やし系とな！
な～んちって！
Ha, I'm kidding.
よかった。
元気になったみたいだね。
Oh, good. You sound like you're feeling better.
まあね。　ぶっちゃけ
あんなヴォイドを見られちゃ→
Yeah, well. Frankly, turning
defiant is the only way to deal
with other people seeing
a Void like that, I guess...
開き直るしかないっていうか…。
There! It's Funeral Parlor!
≪（生徒）いたぞ！　葬儀社だ！
No!
≪（生徒）嫌ぁ！
≪（生徒）逃がすな！！
Don't let her get away!
Confess! You're from Funeral Parlor, aren't you?!
吐けよ！
お前　葬儀社だよな！？
葬儀社の連中って　背中に
タトゥーを入れてるんだってよ。
This says Funeral Parlor people
have tattoos on their backs.
よし　調べろ！
Okay, check it out.
（亞里沙）おやめなさい！
（颯太）てめえら　何やってんだよ！！
Stop that at once!
What are you jerks doing?!
（生徒）うるせえ！　邪魔すんな！
（亞里沙）その手を放しなさい！
Shut up! Don't get in our way!
Get your hands off her!
どうしちゃったんだ　あんな…。
What's going on there?
≪（谷尋）大変だぞ　集！
We've got trouble, Shu!
葬儀社の人間を
政府に差し出したら→
There's a rumor online that turning over
Funeral Parlor members to the government
壁の外に出してもらえるって噂が
ネットに流れてる！
gets you a ticket through the wall!
That's!
そんな…！
ハッ！　いのりと綾瀬は！？
Where are Inori and Ayase?
I-It's okay. I'm only going to check
whether you've got a tattoo.
大丈夫。
ちょっと　タトゥーがないか→
確かめるだけだから。　ねっ？
Okay?
- I'll go check out the old building!
- Got it. Be careful, Tsugumi!
（鶫）私は　旧校舎　見てくる！
分かった。　鶫も気を付けて！
《いのり！》
Inori...
どうしたの？　集。
あっ…。
What's wrong, Shu?
There's an awful rumor spreading.
Did anyone attack you?
ひどいデマが流れてるんだ。
襲われたりしなかった？
It's okay. I haven't seen anyone else so far.
大丈夫。　ここまで
誰にも会わなかったから。
Oh... that's good, then. Let's go!
そう…。　なら　いいんだ。
行こう！
うん。
（難波）前　見たときから
何か変だと思ってたんだ。
You know, I've thought something
was up ever since I first saw you.
君。　学年とクラスは？
What's your year and class?
Out of my way.
どいて！
（数藤）ビンゴか！
Bingo, eh?
このアマ！
You bitch!
Missile Kick!
（鶫）ミサイルゥゥ　キーック！
Let's go, Aya!
行くよ　綾姉！
Why, you!
このぉ…！
（綾瀬）あーっ！
あっ　綾姉！
（綾瀬）何　戻ってきてるの！
Aya!
Why did you come back?!
（鶫）綾姉
置いていけるわけないでしょ！
As if I could leave without you!
Well, aren't you cool!
（数藤）カッコイイ！
[ﾏｲｸ]（亞里沙）予定を前倒して
今から１０分後に→
We're moving up our plans. A student body
meeting will be held in ten minutes.
生徒総会を実施いたします。
All students, please assemble
in the gymnasium immediately.
[ﾏｲｸ]（亞里沙）生徒の皆さんは
至急　体育館に集合してください。
We mustn't be led astray by false rumors!
（亞里沙）デマに踊らされては
いけません！→
待てば　いつか救助は来る。
Help will eventually come if we wait for it.
What we need to do right
now is weather the storm!
耐えることこそ　今　私たちに
必要とされることなのです！
You always say that!
≪（生徒）ずっと　それじゃねーか！≪（生徒）他に言うことないの！？
Don't you have anything else to say?!
That stance isn't going to fly
with the other students anymore.
もう　その姿勢じゃ
みんなには届かないだろ。
How can you say that?
Don't you feel bad for the president?!
何　言ってんだ！
会長が　かわいそうだろ。
《綾瀬たち
こっちにも来てないのか…》
Ayase and Tsugumi aren't here either?
President...
（難波）会長。
今　われわれが聞きたいのは→
What we want to hear right now
is how to avoid getting slaughtered.
虐殺から逃れる方法ですよ。→
とっとと　葬儀社　差し出して
外に出ようって話じゃないですか。
We have to hand over the Funeral Parlor
gang and get out of here, right?
That's a false rumor!
そんなのデマです！
And it's not true that there are
Funeral Parlor members here, either!
葬儀社の人間が　ここにいる
という事実もありません！
Oh yes there are!
（数藤）それが　いたんだって！
In fact, we discovered some ourselves!
何と　俺ら
葬儀社　発見しちゃいましたー！
２人とも！？
Both of them?!
They're wearing our school's uniforms,
彼女たちは
わが校の制服を着てますが→
封鎖される前に　一度でも
見たことある人　いるかな？
but had anyone ever seen
them before the blockade?
葬儀社には
背中にタトゥーがあんだろ！？
Funeral Parlor people have
tattoos on their backs, you know!
えー　マジで！？
じゃあ　ここは一発→
Whoa, for real?
Well then, maybe we should check
that now in front of everyone, eh?!
みんなの前で
確かめた方がいいかなー？
≪（歓声）
- Stop it!
- Funeral Parlor's a criminal gang
that committed bioterrorism!
（亞里沙）およしなさい！
（数藤）葬儀社っていやあ→
ウイルステロを起こした犯罪者だ。許すわけにはいかねえだろ！→
We can't let them get off scot-free!
So...
だから　やるしかねえんだ！
...we'll just have to do it!
ウーッ！
（難波）おっと！→
Whoa there.
おとなしくしてもらおう。
Better be a good girl.
≪（生徒）やれ　やれー！
≪（生徒）やっちまえー！
- Do it!
やれ　やれ！
（生徒）やっちゃえー！
Do it!
やめなさ…。
Stop i...
（生徒たち）やっちまえー！
This is bad!
（谷尋）まずいぞ！　供奉院は完全に場のコントロールを失ってる！
Kuhouin's totally lost control of the room!
If we hand over Funeral Parlor, we'll all be saved!
葬儀社を差し出せば
みんなが助かる！
それは　とっても
すてきなことだろうが！！
And you know that's a wonderful thing!
（綾瀬の悲鳴）
待って！！
Wait!
（生徒たち）うん？
≪（生徒）おい　こいつ…。
Hey, this guy...
He's the one who beat an Endlave yesterday...
≪（生徒）昨日　エンドレイヴを倒した…。
≪（生徒）桜満　集！？
Shu Ouma!
（ざわめき）
Y-You're...
（数藤）て…　てめえは…！
綾瀬から　手を放して！
Take your hands off Ayase.
I'm a member of Funeral Parlor, too.
僕も　葬儀社のメンバーだ。
（ざわめき）
みんなも　悪いけど
ここは　預けてもらえないかな。
Sorry, but could you let me handle this, everyone?
I have an idea.
僕に考えがあるんだ。
ま…　待ってくれ！
W-Wait a second! I brought
Funeral Parlor members! See?
俺は　葬儀社を連れてきたんだ！
ほら！
まだ　学校には　避難してる生徒が
たくさんいるんだ。→
There are still lots of students
taking shelter in the school.
We'll hand these guys over! So please, let us go!
こいつらを差し出す！
だから　助けてくれ！
（ダリル）《うん？》→
That runt... She was with Funeral Parlor?!
《あの　ちんちくりん
葬儀社だったのかよ！？》
Go on, hurry up.
行けよ　おら！
H-Hey, that's careless!
（ダリル）
《お…　おい　うかつだ！》
（銃声）
こ…　これで　俺は…。
So now can I?
（数藤）う…　嘘！？
Y-You're kidding! But...
そんな…。
（銃声）
（難波）な…　なぜだ！？
Why?
Handing over Funeral Parlor should solve things!
葬儀社を差し出したら
解決だろ！→
What the hell is going on?!
いったい　どういうことなんだよ！？
これで分かったでしょ？
政府を頼っても無駄だって。
You get it now, don't you?
Relying on the government won't work.
And you get Shu's Void power too, don't you?
それに　集のヴォイドの力も
分かったでしょ！
This is my Void: the doll-making Hand Scanner!
私のヴォイド
人形を作る　ハンドスキャナー！
（鶫）それで作ったコピー人間も
本物そっくりで→
The human copies I create
with it are just like the real thing,
and you can control them remotely!
しかも　リモコン可能。→
Too awesome, right?!
すご過ぎだよね！
僕には　みんなが
いろんなことが分からなくて→
To me, you all looked afraid because
there was so much you didn't understand.
おびえてるように見えた。
だから
一つ　事実を　はっきりさせた。
So I made one fact perfectly clear.
これで　考えを
先に進められるでしょう？
Now we can move forward
with our thinking, right?
みんなに落ち着いてほしいんだ。
I want you all to calm down.
何だよ　それ！
What the hell?
（難波）国も　お前の力も→
The government... and your powers...
It's all fake!
みんな　いんちきだぁ！！
落ち着いてって言ったでしょ。
僕を怒らせないでよ。
Didn't I tell you to calm down?
Don't make me angry.
昨日も見てもらったように→
Just like you saw yesterday,
we have a way of fighting.
僕らには　戦う方法もある。
So rest easy on that score.
そこは　安心してください。
That's why I want whoever's going
to be the leader to really think.
だから　リーダーになる人には
ちゃんと考えてほしいんです。
To think of a way we'll all be saved.
みんなが助かる方法を…。
それだけです。
お邪魔しました。
That's all.
Excuse me.
待てよ　集。→
Hold up, Shu.
まだ終わってない。
This isn't over yet.
Hey, everybody!
I think Shu's absolutely right!
なあ　みんな！　俺も
集の言うことは　もっともだと思う。
So let me ask you: who on that
stage would make the best leader?
じゃあ　聞くが
今　壇上にいる人間で→
一番　リーダーにふさわしいのは
誰だろうな？
≪（生徒）集！
≪（生徒）桜満　集だ！
Shu!
Shu Ouma!
≪（生徒）集君！
Yahiro, what are you?
谷尋　何を…。
新会長に
桜満　集が就任することに→
Everyone who agrees Shu Ouma should
be our new president, clap your hands!
賛成の者は拍手を！
（拍手）
Yahiro, what was that for?
谷尋！　どういうこと？
俺もサポートする。
やってみろ。
I'll help you with the job. Give it a try.
これが　お前の
「今　やれること」だと思わないか？
Don't you think this is
what you can do right now?
♪♪～
えっ？
What?
今　何て言ったの？　谷尋。
What did you just say, Yahiro?
全生徒を　ゲノムレゾナンス指数でＡからＦに　ランク分けし→
We'll rank all the students on a scale of A to F
based on their genomic resonance values,
その頂点に
集　お前が君臨する。
and you, Shu, will reign over them.
これからは　ヴォイドの価値が
その人間の価値になるんだ。→
From now on, the value of the Void
becomes the value of the person.
いわば　ヴォイドランク制だな。
You could call it the Void ranking system.
Sonna sekai ni nokosareta
boku wa hitori nani wo omoeba ii
♪♪～
Toki wo kasane omoi wo kasane
Sou yatte zutto chikaku ni ite
Atarimae datta kimi ga inaku natte
Sono omosa wo shitta n da
Ano hi sono te wo hanasazu
tsuyoku tsukamaeteta nara
Boku wa kekkyoku hitori de
jikomanzoku shite ita dake
"Maru de kore ja usotsuki da,
kimi no tame toka icchatte"
Sou tsubuyaita kotoba de sae todokanakute
Hashire kimi no moto e
Boku wa nando datte koronde yaru mayotte yaru
Matte ite ima sugu ni iku kara
Donna konnan ga soko ni atte mo